我们昨晚在红花餐厅遇见了你妈
Oh, hey, we ran into your mom at Benihana last night.
好吧 她喜欢那地方
Uh, yeah, she loves that place.
每次厨师把虾铲飞起来
Every time they flip a shrimp in the air,
她就会起身去把它们都夹过来
she practically leaps out of her seat to catch it.
所以我从来不带她去海洋世界
That's why I don't take her to SeaWorld.
我知道... 你可能不想知道
I know you... you don't want to hear it,
但她是和Stuart一起去的
but she was there with Stuart.
没关系
That's fine.
我不在乎
I don't care.
他们去约会 你就不会觉得不爽吗?
It doesn't bug you when they go out on dates?
他们没有约会
They're not dating.
他们只是一起出去吃饭的好朋友
They're just two friends who went out to dinner.
然后他们会回到共住的房子
And then went back to the home they share
然后穿着我妈买的
where they probably fell asleep
情侣睡衣去睡觉
in the matching pajamas she got them
就因为他们都喜欢企鹅
because they both just love penguins.
嘿 很多没在约会的人都喜欢
Hey, lots of people wear matching pajamas
穿情侣睡衣
who aren't dating.
- 比如呢?  - 比如你和你的狗
- Like who?  - Like you and your dog.
别排除他们约会的可能性
Don't rule out the dating.
好吧 我的确不爽
Fine, it bothers me.
高兴了?
You happy?
你觉得自己很不爽
You think you've got problems.
长臂猿是猿类家族中唯一没被归为
The gibbon is the only member of the ape family not classified
类人猿的
as a great ape.
这也算是安慰?
How is this helpful?
所有非人类的猿类都被归为类人猿
All the non-human apes are classified
就一种不是
as great apes except one.
也就是说分类学家给猿类搞出了一个
That means taxonomists created the entire category
更小的分类 就为了排挤出可怜的长臂猿
of lesser ape just to single out the poor gibbon
就像是操场上被排挤的怪小孩
as the weird kid on the playground.
所以那个毛毛的小家伙才是真不爽
Now there's a hairy little fellow with a genuine beef.
但长臂猿根本不知道自己被分在哪类
But the gibbon doesn't know what it's categorized as.
它也许根本不知道自己叫长臂猿
It doesn't even know it's called a gibbon.
没错
True.
抱歉 孩子 你的情况比长臂猿更糟
Sorry, kid, you've got it worse than a gibbon.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季第8集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影纸祝U酱生快么么哒
时间轴: pisces夜
翻译: 影子酱 酥酥祝师护生快 轮子君 工科卫克孟
校对: UU2222222了(马甲)
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
我们给电影夜买了点零食
We brought snacks for movie night.
太棒了
Oh, great.
我想你们应该没买餐巾纸 干净的碗
I don't suppose you also brought napkins, clean bowls,
刀叉和一卷卫生纸吧
utensils and a roll of toilet paper.
都在这里
Right here.
啊!
Ah!
你们最棒啦
You guys are the best.
这些衣服怎么回事?
What's with the clothes?
因为我为了工作买了好多新衣服
Well, with all the new stuff I bought for work,
所以得清理一下衣柜
I needed to make room in my closet.
我是说怎么都折好了?
I meant why are they folded?
无所谓了
But whatever.
噢 这件是什么?
Ooh, what's this?
信不信由你 这是我的毕业舞会礼服
That, believe it or not, is my prom dress.
你还留着?
Wow, you still have it?
我还以为肯定被揉成一团
I just assumed it was balled up
丢在某个谷仓小角落里了呢
in the corner of a barn somewhere.
你们都觉得我过的是什么日子啊?
What kind of teenager did you think I was?
- 放荡  - 随性
- Slutty.  - Easy.
应该是"受欢迎"
The word is "popular."
你的毕业舞会怎么样? 去了吗?
How was your prom? Did you go?
没有 但我是负责打扫的
No, but I was on clean-up crew.
太遗憾了
Aw, that's sad.
其实没那么糟
No, it was okay.
DJ允许我在他收摊前 和我的拖把
The DJ let me dance one slow song with my mop
慢舞了一曲
before he shut down.
所以现在我看到一桶脏水
Whenever I see a bucket of dirty water,
还仿佛能听到"Lady in Red"这歌
I still hear "Lady in Red."
我的毕业舞会也糟透了
My prom was pretty terrible, too.
我很高兴有人邀请我
I was so excited about my date,
但结果他是因为喜欢我朋友
but it turned out he only asked me
才邀请我的
'cause he liked my friend.
他一整晚都在说我的朋友
He spent the whole night talking about her.
我们都懂了 你有朋友 还有舞伴
Okay, we get it, you had a friend and a date.
别炫耀了
Stop bragging.
没关系
Doesn't matter.
毕业舞会很蠢的
Prom is silly anyways.
你说来轻巧 也许你当时的舞伴
Easy for you to say, you probably went
是足球队的队长呢
with the captain of the football team.
不是
No.
我只不过趁他舞伴去吐的时候
I just made out with him a little
和他亲热了一阵
while his date was puking.
我的舞伴会把呕吐物都擦干净
My date would've had to clean that up.
我有个主意
Ooh, I have an idea.
也许我们可以重温一次毕业舞会
Maybe we can have, like, a prom do-over.
肯定会很好玩的
Oh, that would be so much fun.
我们可以装饰一下屋顶 然后让小伙们穿上燕尾服
We could decorate the roof and make the guys wear tuxedos.
我们做个头发 然后跳个慢舞
Ooh, and get our hair done, and slow-dance.
两位 相信我
Okay, guys, trust me,
作为已经去过大概七次毕业舞会的人
as someone who's been to, like, seven proms,
那永远不会有你想的那么美好
it is never as good as you want it to be.
你去过七次?
You went to seven proms?
我来数数
Yeah, let's see.
四次"水下世界" 两次"魔法之夜"
Uh, four "Under the Seas," two "Enchanted Evenings,"
还有一次"难忘今宵"
and one "Night to Remember"
那次... 其实我根本没记住是怎样的
that... I cannot remember for the life of me.
嘿
Hey.
- 嘿  - 嘿 Bernadette呢?
- Hey.  - Hey, where's Bernadette?
她和Amy去买她们毕业舞会的衣服了
She and Amy are out dress shopping for their prom thing.
我收到邀请了
Oh, yeah, I got that Evite.
自从我看过"红粉佳人"后
Ever since I saw Pretty in Pink,
就一直很想去参加美国的毕业舞会
I've wanted to go to an American prom.
结果我又看了"魔女嘉莉"
But then I saw Carrie,
魔女嘉莉: 一部恐怖片
然后就再也不想参加了
and I did not want to go to an American prom.
不过我又看了"一吻定江山"
But then I saw Never Been Kissed,
就又对舞会感兴趣了
and I'm back on the prom bandwagon.
舞会神马的真是难捉摸呢
This prom thing's been a real roller coaster.
Bernie特别兴奋
Bernie's really excited.
我... 我发现 她的声音都变高了
I... I could tell because her voice got so high,
隔壁的小猎犬都被她吓到了
the beagle next door started howling.
你当年参加毕业舞会了吗?
Did you go to your prom?
没
No.
我和"良好教养"约会来着
I had a date with a proper education.
与其穿燕尾服 不如养成良好的习惯
Instead of a tuxedo, I dressed myself in good habits.
我没有喝酒
Instead of spiked punch,
却品尝了知识的美味
I enjoyed the intoxicating flavor of knowledge.
我没有在礼堂跳舞
Instead of dancing in a gym,
却随着AP微积分的韵律...
I shook my booty to the seductive rhythms...
好了 别说了
Okay, okay.
摇摆起舞
Of AP Calculus.
你怎么没和Amy还有Bernadette一起去买东西?
How come you're not shopping with Amy and Bernadette?
我猜你觉得这件事特别无聊?
Let me guess, you think the whole idea is lame?
谁管我是怎么想的? 你觉得呢?
Well, who cares what I think? What do you think?
说实话
Hmm, to be honest,
就算舞会是假的 能和你这样的美女一起参加
it's kind of a dream come true to go to even a fake prom
也算是美梦成真了
with a woman as beautiful as you.
呃 真是谢谢你
Ugh, thanks a lot.
怎么了?
What?
现在要是我拒绝这件事 就真是个小婊砸了
Well, now I can't blow this thing off without being a bitch.
听起来像是在说"好啊好啊"!
That sounds like a "yes"!
噢耶 每个人都回复了“参加”
Ooh, every single person RSVP'd "yes."
太开心了!
This is so exciting!
难道不是吗?
Isn't this exciting?
是啊
Yep.
你看 Stuart都带舞伴来呢
Look, even Stuart's bringing a date.
好想知道是谁啊
I wonder who it is.
你明明知道是谁的
You know exactly who it is.
他会带我妈妈过来
He's gonna bring my mom.
你为什么要邀请他啊?
Why did you even invite him?
因为他是我们的朋友 你们俩应该好好相处
Because he's our friend, and you two need to get along.
而且 他为什么不能带你妈妈?
And why can't he take your mom?
你就是带你妈妈去的舞会啊
You took her to your prom.
她不是我的"舞伴" 她是监护人
I didn't "take" her; she was a chaperone.
我看过你俩跳舞的照片
I saw a picture of you two dancing together.
我... 我还能怎么办?
W... What was I gonna do?
他们放了我们的那首曲子!
They were playing our song!
我忍不了了
I can't take this anymore.
喂
Hello.
Stuart 我们得谈谈
Stuart, we have to talk.
你和我妈妈之间的事 我... 我真的接受不了
This thing with you and my mom, I... I hate it.
我都快疯了
It's making me crazy.
你和我是老朋友了
You and I were friends for years,
可是你现在却要带我妈妈参加我也会出席的舞会?!
and now you're bringing my mother to a party I'm going to?!
这算怎么回事?!
What the hell?!
我才不会带你妈妈去 我有女伴
I'm not bringing your mother, I have a date.
哦 你居然背叛我老妈?
Oh, so now you're cheating on my mother?
哇哦 哇哦 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
你... 你说什么呢?
Wha... What are you talking about?
我和你老妈之间没有发生过任何奇怪的事情
There's nothing weird going on with me and your mother.
Stewie 你的洗澡水快凉了!
Stewie, your bath is getting cold!
我得挂了 拜拜
I got to go, bye.
开门 Penny?
Penny?
开门 penny
Penny.
开门 Penny
你敲门的次数比平时多了
You knocked more than usual.
说不定下次我会着急
Next time I might be in a rush,
这次多敲几下先存着
it's good to have a few in the bank.
好吧 怎么了?
Okay, what's up?
我想和你谈谈Amy和Bernadette
I'd like to discuss this party
举办的舞会
that Amy and Bernadette are throwing.
既然你和我都不太想去
Since you and I are both reluctant to go,
我有一个办法能让我们尽情享受它
I think I've come up with a perfect way for us to enjoy it.
棒啊 什么办法?
Great, how?
我们装作外星人
We pretend we're aliens.
我不太擅长理解人的表情
I'm not the best at reading facial cues,
不过我猜你很感兴趣 而且还想进一步了解我的主意
but I'm gonna say that you love it and want to hear more.
是这样的 在广受欢迎的小说
Now, in the beloved novel
银河系漫游指南中
Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy,
有一个叫做Ford Perfect的外星人假装成人类
an alien named Ford Prefect pretended to be human
混入人群 这样他就可以在银河系漫游指南中
in order to blend in so that he could write an entry about Earth
写一部关于地球的作品
for The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy,
那是一部书中提及的游记
which is a travel book within the actual book,
书名也叫
which is also called
"银河系漫游指南"
The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy.
好吧 我只有一个问题
Okay, just one question.
你在说啥?
What?
重点在于 假装成外星人
My point is, pretending to be an alien is
是我最有用的应对机制 我用过好几次了
a valuable coping mechanism I've used many times.
第一次是去看你的表演的时候
I did it the first time I went to see you in a play.
你一定不知道来自鲸鱼座阿尔法恒星三号的
You had no idea Commander Umfrumf
Umfrumf指挥官就坐在观众席上
of Ceti Alpha Three was in the audience.
哦 别担心 我给你竖了七根大拇指呢
Oh, d... don't worry, he gave you seven thumbs up.
问题在于...
Here's a question...
作为一个假装成人类的外星人 你有没有准备
as an alien pretending to be human, are you planning
在舞会结束之后和Amy进行特定的一些交配仪式?
to engage in any post-prom mating rituals with Amy?
还有交配仪式?
There are post-prom mating rituals?
也不总是有
Not always.
除非你的舞伴开的是有气垫的货车
Unless your date drives a van with an air mattress,
一般都是有的
then always.
好吧 如果这是舞会的一部分的话 我可以接受
Well, if it's part of the prom experience, then I'm open to it.
你开什么玩笑
You're kidding.
就算是外星人 我也是有欲望的啊
I may be an alien, but I have urges.
如果Amy交配的时候想把卵子射入太空
If Amy wants to copulate by firing her eggs into space,
那我很愿意用
well, then, I will happily catch them
我上生殖器的可再生囊去接住它
with the reproductive sac on my upper flermin.
我不太擅长理解人的表情
I'm not the best at reading facial cues,
不过我能看出来你有点感性趣了
but I can see that you're a little turned on.
知道吗 如果你不打算学着自己系领结的话
You know, if you're not gonna learn how to do this,
也可以用那种有夹子的领结
they make some pretty good clip-ons.
蝙蝠侠才不会戴那种领结
Bruce Wayne doesn't wear a clip-on.
蝙蝠侠可不会叫他的室友帮他打领结
Bruce Wayne doesn't make his roommate tie it for him.
他室友是Alfred 而且 没错 他的确帮蝙蝠侠打领结
His name is Alfred, and, yes, he does.
打好了 很完美
There, perfect.
是吗 你确定?
What, are you sure?
这是我第一次参加舞会 我可不想弄错什么
It's my first prom, I want to do it correctly.
我以为你要假扮成外星人
I thought you were gonna pretend to be an alien.
我是想这么做 但是Penny不想
I was, but Penny didn't want to.
你也不想
You didn't want to.
Bernadette Amy Koothrappali Wolowitz都不想
Bernadette, Amy, Koothrappali and Wolowitz didn't want to.
连我都知道雇个人来还是很诡异的
And even I knew it was weird to hire somebody.
那是个酒罐吗?
Was that a flask?
没错
Yes.
我打算接纳所有关于舞会的传统习俗
I've decided to embrace all of the traditions
包括偷偷往大碗里掺酒
associated with prom, including spiking the punch.
你要去掺酒?
You're gonna put alcohol in the punch?
哦 不 这只是石榴汁
Oh, no, this is pomegranate juice.
这就像是高中时捣鬼作怪 只不过是用
It's all the fun of high school high jinks
石榴汁代替大量的抗氧化剂
with the cell-protecting zip of antioxidants.
如果你把牛仔裤和皮衣扯烂后再穿
If you had ripped jeans and a leather jacket,
你大概就是迪士尼频道最霸气的家伙了
you'd be like the toughest kid on the Disney Channel.
那么 今晚还有什么别的打算吗?
So, anything else planned for tonight?
噢 什么都想干
Oh, everything.
拍拍照片 跳跳慢舞
Getting our picture taken, slow-dancing,
当选舞会国王
being elected prom king.
向大家指明国王不是选举产生的
Pointing out that kings aren't elected.
这样应该就能脱身了
It's gonna be off the hook.
当你在舞会上
And while you're at it,
我知道你这个年龄 你的荷尔蒙会飙升
I know that at this age your hormones are raging,
但是不要因为你的所有朋友们都在和别人上床
but just because all your friends are having sex
你就也跟着这么做
doesn't mean you have to.
你这么说是为什么?
Why would you say that?
你懂的 因为...
You know, 'cause...
因为很多人是在舞会之夜破的处
'cause a lot of people lose their virginity on prom night.
Penny也这么暗示了
Penny implied the same thing.
这是真的吗?
Is this true?
放松一下 开个玩笑而已
Just relax, it's a joke.
你又没有荷尔蒙
You don't have hormones.
哇 你太漂亮了
Wow, you look amazing.
谢谢 你也是
Thank you, so do you.
Sheldon 你看起来好帅
Sheldon, you look so handsome.
谢谢你
Thank you.
Amy不美吗 Sheldon?
Sheldon, doesn't Amy look hot?
这可是会让上生殖器硬起来
That's got to put some starch in the upper flermin.
那是什么?
What's that?
噢 那是个长在他两侧肩胛骨中间的
Oh, it's a scaly genital organ
鳞状生殖器
that grows between his shoulder blades.
跳舞的时候尽量别碰到它
Try not to touch it when you're dancing.
抱歉
Excuse me.
你要去哪里?
Where are you going?
我做不到
I can't do this.
而且告诉你 Leonard
And for your information, Leonard,
上生殖器不长在我的肩胛骨中央
the upper flermin doesn't grow between my shoulder blades,
它长在我脖子上的肚脐眼里
it grows out of the belly button on my neck.
他说得没错 我想的是下生殖器
He's right, I was thinking of the lower flermin.
喔 我要 呃 我要发短信给Stuart 告诉他我们快到了
Ooh, I'll, uh, text Stuart, let him know we're close.
好漂亮的纹身
That's a neat tattoo.
哦 谢谢 这是圣诞夜惊魂里的Sally
Oh, thanks, it's Sally from Nightmare before Christmas.
嗷 那部电影好萌的
Aw, that movie's so cute.
你喜欢她是因为你们俩头发都是红色的吗?
Do you like her because you both have red hair?
呃 有那么一点吧 不过主要是因为她浑身都是伤疤
Uh, a little, but more that she's covered in scars
而且她还可以把自己的四肢拆下来再缝回去
and can pull her own limbs off and sew them back on.
我喜欢灰姑娘
I like Cinderella.
你知道在原著里
Did you know, in the original book,
她的姐姐们为了能穿进玻璃鞋
the sisters cut off their toes with knives
把自己的脚趾头都割下来了?
in order to fit in the glass slipper?
我喜欢"Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo"
I like "Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo."
Bibbidi-Bobbidi-Boo: 电影仙履奇缘2中的插曲
嘿 Stuart和他的女伴来了
Hey, here comes Stuart and his date.
噢 她真漂亮
Oh, she's cute.
天啊
Oh, my God.
怎么了?
What?
那是Jeanie
That's Jeanie.
那就是Jeanie?!
That's Jeanie?!
- 谁是Jeanie?  - 别说出来
- Who's Jeanie?  - Don't say it.
那是Howard上过的表妹
That's Howard's cousin that he had sex with.
她是我的第二代堂表妹
She is my second cousin.
我们才15岁... 我刚说了"别说出来"
We were 15... I just said, "Don't say it."
不不不 没事的
No, it's okay.
他早就告诉过我这个故事了
He told me that story a long time ago.
Raj 怎么这样!
Raj!
那是我们第一次约会
It was our first date,
没人说话 气氛很尴尬
there was an awkward silence.
我还能说什么?
What was I supposed to say?
喔 真漂亮
Oh, it's beautiful.
姑娘们手艺真不错
Oh, the girls really did a nice job.
嗷...
Aw...
我知道一开始我有点不情愿
I know I wasn't into this before,
不过作为第一个带你参加舞会的人 我很荣幸
but I'm so glad I get to take you to your first prom.
为什么你觉得我没去过舞会?
What makes you think I didn't go to my prom?
- 我去啦  - 那好 你和谁一起去的呀?
- I went.  - Well, who'd you go with?
我带了一个叫"寂寞"的小姑娘
I took a little lady I like to call loneliness.
哦...
Aw...
没事的
Aw, it's all right.
我们最后还和她的朋友"羞耻"
We ended up having a threesome
来了个3P 所以...
with her friend humiliation, so...
嗯 如果当时我在场还看见你一个人的话
Well, if I would have been there and saw you alone,
我会邀请你跳支舞的
I would've asked you to dance.
不 你不会的
No, you wouldn't have.
这可轮不到你说
Well, you don't know that.
当时我还没经历青春期迅速长高的阶段
It was before my growth spurt.
什么 你已经长高过了?
What, that already happened?
真好笑
Very funny.
嗯 你也不可能邀请我
Well, you wouldn't have asked me either.
我会啊
I would have asked you.
在我的脑海里
In my head.
在我回家的路上
On the way home.
还在大哭一场的时候
While I was having a good cry.
Sheldon 我能进来吗?
Sheldon, can I come in?
我不觉得这是个好主意
I don't think that's a good idea.
为什么不?
Why not?
按一个在线留言板说的
According to an online message board,
我现在可能是恐慌症发作
I may be having a panic attack.
跟SoccerMom09是同样的问题
SoccerMom09 had similar symptoms.
但公平地讲 那天那对双胞胎真是棘手
But to be fair, the twins were a real handful that day.
你让我很担心
You're making me worry.
发生什么事了?
What's going on?
发生的事就是我们要参加毕业舞会了
What's going on is we're about to go to a prom.
像我们这样的年轻恋人
And there's a great deal of pressure
参加被Bob Eubanks先生称为狂欢的东西
on young couples like us to engage in
真的压力很大啊
what Mr. Bob Eubanks called making whoopee.
什么压力?
What pressure?
我只是说你看起来很帅
All I said was you look handsome.
你能不能把门打开?
Can you please open the door?
不光是这个
It's not just that.
Leonard和Penny也评论过
Leonard and Penny also made comments about it.
而且我又不瞎
And I'm not blind.
当我看到自己穿着礼裤时的屁股
Even I looked twice when I saw my posterior
都忍不住多看了一眼
in these tuxedo pants.
于是我在你阿姨Glady家见到了Jeanie
So, I met Jeanie at your Aunt Gladys'.
她给了我马尼舍维茨酒
She passed me the Manischewitz,
我看了这张脸一眼
I took one look at this punim,
就几乎激动万分
and I almost plotzed on the kugel.
我谈起印度时 听起来是不是也是这样?
Is this what I sound like when I talk about India?
我妈妈对这事没意见吗?
So, my mother's okay with this?
你妈妈为什么会对我和Stuart在一起有意见呢?
Why would your mother have a problem with me and Stuart?
因为他们之间有着奇怪 不合适的关系
'Cause they have a weird, inappropriate relationship.
比你和我在我爸爸的卡罗拉里干的事还奇怪吗?
Weirder than what you and I did in my dad's Corolla?
情况真混乱
This is so messed up.
我知道 我看得超开心
I know, I'm having the best time.
你为什么要来呢?
Why would you even come to this?
你不知道我要来吗?
Didn't you know I'd be here?
都很久以前的事了 Howard
It was a long time ago, Howard.
而且你们不过是表亲 谁在乎?
And you're only second cousins, who cares?
这么说你知道 但还是把她带来了?
So, you knew and you brought her anyway?
你觉得她对Howard来说足够好 对我来说不够了?!
Oh, so she's good enough for Howard, but not for me?!
是啊
Yeah.
是啊 你跟你自己的妈妈和表妹
Yeah, go have weird relationships
发展奇怪关系去吧
with your own mother and cousin.
这是他的地盘
This is his turf.
对
Yeah.
我当时可能没邀请你跳舞
Well, I might not have asked you to dance then,
- 但我现在要请你跳  - 又没有音乐
- but I will ask you now.  - There's no music.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我们来制造自己的音乐
We'll make our own music.
天啊 现在谁是呆子?
My God, who's the dork now?
谢谢你穿了平底鞋
Thank you for wearing your flats.
谢谢你穿了高跟鞋
Thank you for wearing your heels.
嗯
Mmm.
看看我
Look at me.
我在跟舞会上最漂亮的女孩跳舞
Dancing with the prettiest girl at the prom.
想拍张我们的照片
Want to take a picture of us and send it
发给你象棋俱乐部的老朋友们吗?
to your old friends in the chess club?
我几年前给他们发过一张你的比基尼照
I sent them a bikini shot of you years ago.
这感觉真好
This is nice.
我有点希望其他人不要来了
I kind of wish no one else was coming.
我知道 我也是
I know, me, too.
但是没有戏剧性场面的舞会应该也很有趣
But it will be fun to have a prom without all the drama.
Howie 放开他!
Howie, get off of him!
只要他还想顺着我家家谱往上爬 我就不放!
Not until he stops humping his way up my family tree!
Sheldon 这样太傻了
Sheldon, this is silly.
我不会再错过一场舞会了
I'm not missing another prom.
我要上楼了
I'm going upstairs now.
再见
Good-bye.
我当时真的觉得你很漂亮
I really did think you looked pretty.
真的?
You did?
是的
Yes.
漂亮得让我心慌意乱
So much so that I started to panic.
你放松一下
Well, you can relax.
你觉得我漂亮也不代表
Just because you think I look pretty
我们就要一起度过这个夜晚
doesn't mean we have to spend the night together.
你是因为想去舞会 才想和我一起的吗?
Were you hoping we would because it's a prom?
我一直都希望和你在一起
I'm always hoping.
但今晚我只是想跟你度过一段愉快时光
But tonight I just wanted to have a nice time with you.
可能还能跟有胳膊的人跳舞
And maybe dance with someone who has arms.
谢谢你的理解
Thank you for understanding.
我当然理解
Of course I understand.
Sheldon 听着
Sheldon,
还有句话我一直想说
there's something else I've been wanting to say,
但我说之前 我...
but before I do, I just...
我希望你知道 你不用给我回应的
I want you to know that you don't have to say it back.
我知道你还没准备好
I know you're not ready,
我也不希望你只是因为社交要求
and I don't want you to say it
而说这句话...
just because social convention dictates...
我也爱你
I love you, too.
你说出来了
You said it.
无可否认 我对你的感情
There's no denying I have feelings for you
用其它方式表达不了
that can't be explained in any other way.
我以前只是以为我脑子里有寄生虫
I briefly considered that I had a brain parasite.
但现在看来那说法更牵强了
But that seems even more farfetched.
唯一的解释就是爱
The only conclusion was love.
我知道怎么回事
I know what's happening.
这是恐慌症发作
This is a panic attack.
SoccerMom09说要躺下 把脚抬起来
SoccerMom09 says to lie down with your feet elevated.
好的
Okay.
哇哦 哇哦 等等
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
我爱你也不代表
Just because I love you doesn't mean
女孩可以进我的房间了
girls are allowed in my room.
好的
Okay.
要拍了...
Here we go...
说"茄子"!
Say "Cheese"!
说"表亲"!
Say "Cousin"!
说...
Say...
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
稍等一下 抱歉
Hang on, sorry.
嘿 Debbie
Hey, Debbie.
我... 对 对 我和Jeanie在一起呢
I... Yeah, yeah, I'm here with Jeanie.
好的 但我们只是朋友
Okay, but we're just friends.
是... 好 我得走了
It's... Yeah. I got to go.